And how is Reprit's value proposition
different from that of its
closest competitors?
First of all, we are completely
fixated on our ideal customer
profile, so not technical users,
what we essentially call knowledge workers
.  If you know how to use Excel, there's no
reason why you can't use
repletit.  Then there's this whole issue
of infrastructure that we build around
our agent.  If you want to use a
database, use the database we
offer you, but we give you the guarantees
that it runs on a cloud provider, we have
Audit Log, we have Stock to, we have
all the certifications you need.
If you're a
random person working in HR and you decide to
build a software that manages part
of your HR chart, you can ship it
within your company and IT will be
completely on your side because we pass
all the security checks you need.
At the same time, if I had given
cloud code to that person, even if
they had managed to build the software I
had in mind, there
would still have to be a handover to
timid engineering and they would have had to do
all the security checks and everything else
that is needed to actually put it into
production.  No.